Hi!
Now what we're going to do is we're going to actually bake our squash for a little bit.
You have your mixture and squash.
Right over the cooking tray we're going to use this.
Just pour a little bit on there.
Evenly coat that.
If you have a brush, you can.
If not, you can throw in a piece of squash and move it around.
A quick little ways to get around stuff if you don't have it.
A paper towel works just nice. What you want to do is you want to lay your squash in here. We're not going to cook for too long because these should be thin enough so they cook fast.
After you've got your first layer, go ahead and pour half your mixture over that.
What you want to do is go ahead and put the other half of the squash on there.
At this point, we're going to go ahead and put the rest of the marinade on top.
Make sure you get all of it on there.
Move the seasoning around.
You're going to bake for about 5 minutes.